I fear that the world will not accept
her, but she is a part of it all the same.
The true human, like anyone else.
It was a success.
This is the first step.
I'm confident that this will bring
peace to this planet someday.
Sign Dr.
Vegapunk, direct to Rodman's.
It's a laboratory for peace.
Thank you.
We're all set to take out the Vegapunks.
We've got them trapped like rats.
Now then, how do we drag
the rats from their nest?
That frontier dump
won't be easy to breach.
Yeah, tell me about it.
You know the Navy's rules about
attacking Emperors, don't you?
I don't acknowledge
Straw Hat as an Emperor.
Suit yourself, then.
They move quickly.
All of the sailing routes are blocked.
They've likely seized every
ship on the island by now.
We still have Vega Force One, but
it can't operate beyond Egghead.
They've turned our lab into a kill zone
Who will do the killing?
Time to avenge Atlas, gang?
Our objective right now is to escape!
Not to engage them!
But even so, a battle may be inevitable.
What's that?
I wasn't listening.
I gave myself chills.
Oh, hey, Lilith, buddy?
I don't think they can
even get up here right now.
So let's just put a pin
in the whole killing idea!
And cool our collective jets. Yeah?
Enough, Lilith.
Charging in blindly will
only make things worse.
Did you lose your spine or something?
These butt wipes are trying to take us
out and you don't even want to fight back?
What's your deal?
You are losing sight of our goal.
We need to get Stella
safely off the island.
We're not getting anywhere with
the whole armada in the way.
No, no.
Everyone just settle down, please.
We are Stella's satellites.
Our duty is to ensure his
safety even at our own peril.
We need to keep our priorities straight.
You running wild won't help anything.
This goody-two-shoes shit
is gonna get you killed.
And I won't miss ya. Just saying.
Yes. Noted.
Eureka!
I just thought of another invention!
But what can I -
I don't have enough time
or resources or manpower!
to conduct the research!
Where's my asses to be?
Oh, you were right there.
That's meowsic to my ears, Joshu!
Oh, poor Sentomaru, you took my side
and ended up like this. I'm sorry.
What should we do?
There is one other person on this
island who we could call for help.
We can't just expose our friend like that!
The government would start a manhunt!
We need to punk up and
handle these ourselves.
I suppose you're right.
Anyway, that's the situation.
I can't leave because I'm
stuck in the lab. Stella, no!
Making that call is a death sentence!
Stop!
Now that you know the stakes, I
require your help out of this mess.
How could you?
Have you no shame?
Of course, Doctor.
I expected your call and I'm on the move.
Calick.
Did you hear that, everyone?
Help me, Zong's-a-vay!
Well, I guess we are
in a bit of a pickles.
Looks like we have no choice.
I don't feel great about this, but we need
someone to handle CP0 so we can escape!
Come on, guys, let's get Stella
on that ship! Works for me.
Then I'll take Vegaforce One and
carry the ship to one of the ports.
Good.
Hurry and get it done.
What the hell is wrong with you?
You just can't resist
bossing everyone around, huh?
We're wasting time.
Let's begin the escape at once.
You're doing it again!
All right, seems we've got a plan.
I recrase our passage on your ship.
I assume there's enough
space. You know it. Let's go.
That is to say, I recrase our room
for seven. For seven? Ah, sweet!
The other Vegapunks are coming, too?
Seven of the world's best
scientists on my ship!
Are you kidding me?
This deal keeps getting worse and worse.
All of the Vegapunks are coming with us?
So then, that means we get
another lady on the ship?
Welcome to the team, Millet!
I'm so happy to have you with us!
Vegapunk!
I'm gonna squish you
like a bug! What a mess!
She forgot why she was mad!
All she can think about
now are those bugs!
Funny!
Please don't kick Mr.
Appelman's ass!
I said I'd help him escape!
Can you at least wait till later?
No, he's dead!
That sounds bad.
Labophase Defense System,
Frontier Dome now deactivated.
What?
Who could have done this?
And for what purpose?
Talk to me, Pythagoras!
What's going on?
I don't know.
The interception protocol was
lifted without any warning.
We're wide open.
If the enemy heads for the
Labophase now, we can't stop them.
Damn it!
Check the control room!
Is anyone in there?
Control room?
Control room? It's empty!
I don't know how, but it seems the
barrier was deactivated remotely!
Who could have pulled
off a stunt like that?
Frontier Dome has been deactivated.
Did something happen
up there? Let's hurry.
This is our chance, right?
Who cares why? I do.
Could be a trap.
Or it could be our only opening.
We would be fools to let it pass us by.
This is entirely too convenient.
I know we want in there.
We can't complete our
mission if the barrier's up.
Trap or not, this is an
improvement in my book.
I'm going for it you snooze you lose
there
see
that lemon
squeezy and nobody?
Exploded what do you know well it wasn't
a trap let's bust the door down and go!
Get them this is our golden opportunity
now wolves are at your door!
Poor Vegapunk, fortune has failed
you at the worst possible time.
Is that Straw Hat's ship over there?
I see now.
That's why it wasn't on
the coast when we arrived.
A giant robot too?
It's an eyesword. Destroy it.
I'll be done in a jiffy.
And that takes care of the dishes.
Looks like I've still got plenty of
time, so I think I'll swab the deck next.
I should probably look into that
ominous alarm, but I'm sure it's fine.
Impicc-kick-gay-slicer!
What the hell?
Pearl, what's going on?
Are we under attack?
Who was that?
Can't you see I was trying to take a nap?
Roronoa!
Shaka! Code Red!
The Frontier Dome is up again,
but CP0 is already inside!
Damn it. We're too late.
They're trying to destroy
the Straw Hat ship.
Yes, but lucky for us, a few crew
members stayed behind to protect it.
We need to send backup.
If we don't, we'll lose our only escape!
Well, well, seems violence is the answer.
Now step back and leave
the feds to kill it.
And let you jeopardize everyone's safety?
Not a chance.
Bonnie, sure took off.
Where'd she go?
Hey!
We're here, guys!
Huh?
Luffy! Chopper!
Geefey!
Oh, man!
You wouldn't believe all
the cool stuff we saw!
Even found a robot!
We agreed to take all
the Vegapunks with us.
We'd better hurry up! Aw!
But we just got here!
We haven't even seen the whole lab yet!
Can't we stay a little longer?
Maybe if you want to get murdered.
Look, we'd love to stay, but
this is a government island.
Also, Lucci is here.
We hate that guy.
What was that?
He came from outside.
Cipherpole will show up any second now.
We'll get trapped in another fight.
Aw, come on.
Oh, have you guys seen Bonnie?
She's got long pink hair
and she's kind of mean.
Bonnie, huh? Huh?
Is that the girl you were
hanging with down in the city?
Yeah, that's her.
She's sort of trying to
kill Vegapunk right now.
What?
Why would she do that?
By the way, where is he?
He was here a second ago.
Die, Vegapunk!
Dammit!
Face me, you coward!
Get back here!
Stupid! Bonnie!
I don't have time for...
Please, please!
I do want to speak with
you, just without the...
Violence, if you don't mind, go to hell!
Bonnie! Woo!
I'm not letting you go!
You're going to look
me in the eye and tell
me if you can turn back my father or not!
Yes or no, live or die!
It's not that simple.
I'm sorry.
I can't.
Then you've made your choice!
This is for my father!
I have a good reason!
I promise you!
God damn it!
I don't know.
Something fell from the wall.
It's Bartholomew Kuma.
What?
Where did he come from?
Actually, I think I heard in the
news that he escaped from Marie Joie.
But why is he here?
The Celestial Dragons called
him their invincible slave.
He's huge.
A former warlord of the sea,
Bartholomew Kuma, has appeared.
He's currently in the northeast,
near the entrance of Muldeross.
All Marines, dispatch immediately.
All citizens must evacuate the area.
Do not approach Cape
under any circumstance.
He's property of the Celestial Dragons.
He no longer has a human body.
His current programming is unknown.
Repeat, for your own safety, all
citizens must evacuate at once.
It hurts.
I must have broken my
leg when I fell down.
Oh, no.
Zapoodle.
I'm going to get him.
They need the med team.
I'm sorry, Bonnie. Oh!
Distorted future!
Now you die!
I've been singled!
It's time to end it!
Please just listen, even if you can't be!
Change!
Now,
sir,
why do I have to be a baby?
and bought us his gems.
Oh, my golden years.
Bonnie,
give back the shorty years of my life.
Stop your whining.
My powers don't work on
living things forever.
It'll wear off, but not
before we're done here.
Now out with it.
What was your good reason?
You said you had one.
So spit it out.
Why did you kill my father?
If I tell you, it will
only bring you more pain.
I'm sorry.
I want to help. I truly do.
But no! What?
I made a promise with
your father. You see?
Look, it's Kuma.
He's climbing straight up the red line.
Surely they're going to stop
him before he gets to the top.
Before he lost his humanity, I swore to him
that I'd never tell you why it happened.
You had a reason to kill my father,
but you can't say it? Screw you!
Who would believe that crap?
Do you think I'm stupid?
Of course I don't!
It's the truth!
So please let me go!
Kuma chose to give up
his humanity on his own!
It wasn't me!
It was his choice and no
one else's! You're lying!
You're saying he chose this hell?
That he chose to abandon me?
You killed him!
It was hell for me as well!
I can't even stand to remember it!
Your father is an extraordinary man.
I'm proud to call him my friend.
I truly care for him.
I swear to you and that is exactly
why I won't please a word you bastard!
I'm sick of your self-serving lies.
I'm not gonna let you trick me.
This is abuse.
I can't take it.
It's just a broken contraption bunny.
It has nothing to do with Kuma, I promise.
Lying again.
OIL SHOCK, GO!
STUPID BODY!!!
You're wrong.
Please, no!
A person's thoughts? Indeed.
There was a scholar in the vest blue
who made a revolutionary discovery.
They said people lose 21 grams
of weight at the moment of death.
So, you might say that's
the weight of a human soul.
Of course, there's much
more testing to do,
but I think it's proof
that the soul exists.
In fact, I'm certain of it.
I'm afraid this one might be beyond me.
On the contrary, you're an expert.
It is similar to your power.
A person's pain is illangible, yes?
But you can take it from their body
and transfer it to someone else.
Nerves create electrical signals, and
you can move them without using wires.
Let's compare it to mental images instead
mental images yes
memories and other images.
You see in your mind's eye are also
signals from nerve cells how much
do they weigh how Big are they that's
what i want to know fascinating
isn't it you want me to take out my
memories and Show them to you are
you trying to humiliate me i'm begging
you do it for the sake of science I
won't show them to anyone pretty
please forget it i could never trust
you with something as Sensitive as
that oh come now i must know stop it
you must not touch that pole it is
suffering In given form you could die
you know kuma's power the pain he
emerges is unbearable it will kill you
You're wrong it's not pain dad
Shoot Kuma down on sight!
He cannot reach Marie's wall!
Light him up!
All right, he's down!
Hurry!
Surround him!
Evacuate the area!
It's dangerous!
I know my father's power,
so I know what I'm seeing,
and it isn't pain.
Finish him off!
Pull back!
The truth is, these are his memories.
What?
How did Lucci get up here so fast?
Unfortunately, it seems there
was a glitch in the system.
At least the Sunny will still be okay.
There's no way they'll
beat Zoro and Brook.
It's two against three.
I wouldn't be so sure just yet.
No, look at the monitor.
I'm afraid their odds
are much worse than that.
No way the Seraphim are
here too it's two of
your crew mates against
seven killing machines.
We didn't order them to come up here
they're stuck with us either way.
The dome closed right after they came in.
Oh come on they snuck the Seraphim
in while the dome was down.
No fair.
Actually I don't think CP0
intended to bring them here at all.
Say what?
It's a feature of the Seraphim.
In some circumstances, they can
make basic decisions on their own.
They must have figured out that the
Dome would be back soon and made a move.
Yes, but this could work in our favor.
We can turn this battle around.
How would we do that?
They've got us backed
into a corner, don't they?
Our orders outrank Gates on the
Seraphim scale of authority.
Once we reach them, they'll answer to us.
Then we better get over there and give
them some orders before it's too late.
Hang on, I'm coming, straw heads!
Hey, wait for me!
Are you taking this seriously?
Of course I am! Good!
Let's hope those two can hold out.
Don't dawdle.
We're counting on you two.
Hey, no!
You're not a boss!
Zoro!
I've got to hit you with
everything I've got!
Oh, this is bad!
Even Zoro and Brooke can't
take on all of them at once!
In that case, I'll go back them up!
Good luck out there, pal!
I'm just gonna hide in here!
I mean, guard the base!
Guess Moss Head won't live
to see the One Piece, huh?
What a shame.
Your crewmates need you, you idiot!
Get out there and help!
Did my darling Nami just
give me an order? I'm on it!
Consider me your own personal seraphim!
Sanji Fem is here to do
anything you ask him to!
Wait!
Why do I have to save Moss Head?
Because we need him, Curly Fem!
Now come on, we gotta burn!
This is a lucky break.
I've been waiting to
settle the score with you.
Time for round two.
Ready?
Let's go!
Hold on.
I thought he was a giraffe.
That's what he's supposed to be.
But I guess he does look kind of weird.
Well, whatever.
He's getting cut down either way.
You think it'll be that easy, do you?
Just try me!
Look after the ship, okay?
Roger that.
You better not flinch!
Nose pistol!
That's just a sample.
Here comes the main course.
Tarrasque blast!
Plenty more where that came from!
This isn't anything new to me.
I fought a guy with a
long neck in Wano, too.
Now get the hell away from our ship!
We'll take out the lab
and Vegapunk with it!
Destroy everything in sight!
No!
The Seraphim are aiming for the lab!
We're trapped!
If our allies fail, we'll all
be crushed! What? Crushed?
Oh, no.
Whether you defeat me or not,
there's no getting out of this alive.
Really showboating
today, aren't you, kids?
Those bastards.
Keep this up, and we'll have
the mission done before lunch!
Stussy, you...
Kaku!
Stussy, what are you doing?
Answer me!
Oh, nothing.
Just putting a bad boy to sleep.
Do me a favor, Lucci.
Why don't you join him?
That's gotta be the biggest
fish I've ever seen!
They say there's something
unusual about these waters.
This should be fun.
Is that an island?
Kid, wake up.
We've got land up ahead.
Should we drop anchor?
That's a dumb question.
We've made it this far, haven't we?
So there's no island left for us to fear.
Hold up. Wait.
The hell is that?
I think I might know where we are.
It's the island of the giants, Elbath.
Interesting.
Absolutely not.
Are you kidding me?
We're headed out for the
Egghead mission any minute now.
I'm not going to lend you my
troops at a time like this.
Are they too busy removing
that stick from your caboose?
Laugh it up all you want.
My answer's still no.
Besides, that island's an emperor's turf.
Did you get clearance to invade?
I bet the brass popped
a vein when you asked.
I have to ask.
Huh?
Come on, how many decades
have you been a marine?
It'll all work out.
I'm here, by the way.
Wait, what?
El Mabo!
Get your butt out here!
What?
Is it a pirate?
It sounds like they've come
here to take revenge on Helmepo.
No. Wait!
Oh, good!
There you are, boy!
Didn't keep me waiting.
My central guard!
I'm so glad you're here!
Gobi got caught by Blackbeard.
It wasn't his fault.
He was so brave, but I was helpless.
I couldn't do anything.
Would you stop your blubbering already?
You look like a fool.
I just want to help them.
Glad to hear it.
Hop aboard.
Pirate Island?
You think that'll scare
off an old marine like me?
We'll give those bastards a
beating on their own turf.
We're going to kick down their
front door and rescue Kali!
I said broken!
I'm always looking at my head in my head.
I'm still looking for the future!
I'm looking for
a real promise.
I'm in my heart.